{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Grading Contractors","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40324/":{"taskOID":40324,"originalTaskOID":40324,"setID":621,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":5538,"questionDisplayText":"Purpose of Grading","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the purpose of grading?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2074,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Drainage before installing landscaping","answerDisplayText":"Drainage before installing landscaping","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3149,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Improving existing drainage","answerDisplayText":"Improving existing drainage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4776,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Pond digging","answerDisplayText":"Pond digging","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1163,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Building or deck foundation digging","answerDisplayText":"Building or deck foundation digging","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1029,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Berms","answerDisplayText":"Berms","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2091,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Driveway preparation","answerDisplayText":"Driveway preparation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5577,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Septic tank and leach field","answerDisplayText":"Septic tank and leach field","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5539,"questionDisplayText":"Surveyed and Drawings Complete","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Has the site been surveyed and have landscape drawings been completed?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":5538,"questionDisplayText":"Purpose of Grading","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the purpose of grading?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2074,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Drainage before installing landscaping","answerDisplayText":"Drainage before installing landscaping","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3149,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Improving existing drainage","answerDisplayText":"Improving existing drainage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4776,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Pond digging","answerDisplayText":"Pond digging","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1163,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Building or deck foundation digging","answerDisplayText":"Building or deck foundation digging","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1029,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Berms","answerDisplayText":"Berms","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2091,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Driveway preparation","answerDisplayText":"Driveway preparation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5577,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Septic tank and leach field","answerDisplayText":"Septic tank and leach field","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":2074,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Drainage before installing landscaping","answerDisplayText":"Drainage before installing landscaping","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3149,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Improving existing drainage","answerDisplayText":"Improving existing drainage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4776,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Pond digging","answerDisplayText":"Pond digging","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1163,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Building or deck foundation digging","answerDisplayText":"Building or deck foundation digging","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1029,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Berms","answerDisplayText":"Berms","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2091,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Driveway preparation","answerDisplayText":"Driveway preparation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5577,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Septic tank and leach field","answerDisplayText":"Septic tank and leach field","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5539,"questionDisplayText":"Surveyed and Drawings Complete","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Has the site been surveyed and have landscape drawings been completed?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"semThreeIcons":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/40324/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40324,"taskName":"Landscape - Minor Grading or Resloping","taskDescription":"Grade or Reslope Grounds for Landscaping","xmTaskDescriptor":"Grading Contractors","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":149,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Grade Land Grading Reslope back","textMessagingName":"Grading","rolloverLongDesc":"Typically done immediately after initial construction, in response to a drainage problem or in preparation for a radical re-landscaping project","rolloverShortDesc":"Alter the terrain to improve drainage or aesthetics.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Grade or Reslope Grounds for Landscaping.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Grading Contractors \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Landscape Sloping - HomeAdvisor","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":47,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Minor Grading or Resloping","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Landscape - Minor Grading or Resloping","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Landscape Project","urlName":"Landscape-Minor-Grading-or-Resloping","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Grading Contractors - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Costs \u0026 Reviews","searchKeywords":"Grade,Land,Grading,Reslope,back,backyard,front,lawn,landscapers,draining,drainage,architects,architect,pool, irrigation","emcCategoryOid":-12046,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":621,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"isCookielessUser":true}